let questions = [
    {
        question_number: 1,
        question: "Who is the most decorated Olympian of all time, with the highest number of Olympic ",
        correctAnswer: "Michael Phelps",
        choices: [
            "Usain Bolt",
            "Michael Phelps",
            "Simone Biles",
            "Carl Lewis"
        ]
    },

    {
        question_number: 2,
        question: "Which football club won the UEFA Champions League in 2021?",
        correctAnswer: "Chelsea",
        choices: [
            "Bayern Munich",
            "Manchester City",
            "Real Madrid",
            "Chelsea"
        ]
    },

    {
        question_number: 3,
        question: "In which sport do competitors try to hit a shuttlecock over a net using rackets?",
        correctAnswer: "Badminton",
        choices: [
            "Badminton",
            "Squash",
            "Table Tennis",
            "Tennis"
        ],
    },

    {
        question_number: 4,
        question: "Which athlete is known as 'The Greatest' in the sport of boxing?",
        correctAnswer: "Muhammad Ali",
        choices: [
            "Muhammad Ali",
            "Mike Tyson",
            "Sugar Ray Robinson",
            "Floyd Mayweather Jr."
        ],
    },

    {
        question_number: 5,
        question: "Which country has won the most gold medals in the history of the Winter Olympics?",
        correctAnswer: "Norway",
        choices: [
            "United States",
            "Norway",
            "Russia",
            "Germany"],
    },
    {
        question_number: 6,
        question: "In which city did the 2016 Summer Olympics take place?",
        correctAnswer: "Rio de Janeiro",
        choices: [
            "Rio de Janeiro",
            "London",
            "Beijing",
            "Sydney"],
    },
    {
        question_number: 7,
        question: "Which golfer has the most major championship wins in history?",
        correctAnswer: "Jack Nicklaus",
        choices: [
            "Tiger Woods",
            "Jack Nicklaus",
            "Arnold Palmer",
            "Phil Mickelson"],
    },
    {
        question_number: 8,
        question: "Which sport is associated with the Stanley Cup?",
        correctAnswer: "Ice Hockey",
        choices: [
            "Ice Hockey",
            "Basketball",
            "American Football",
            "Baseball"],
    },
    {
        question_number: 9,
        question: "Which country has won the most Women's World Cup titles in football (soccer)?",
        correctAnswer: "United States",
        choices: [
            "United States",
            "Brazil",
            "Germany",
            "Norway"],
    },
    {
        question_number: 10,
        question: "Who won the NBA MVP (Most Valuable Player) award for the 2020-2021 season?",
        correctAnswer: "Nikola Jokić",
        choices: [
            "LeBron James",
            "Giannis Antetokounmpo",
            "Kevin Durant",
            "Nikola Jokić"],
    }
];